Guide to the Center for International Policy Records, 1960-2016 and undated; 1960-ongoing RL.00205
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Adam Isacson Papers, 1987-2006 and undated
  - Travel, 1998-2005, 18 folders
    - Ecuador-Colombia Border (2 folders), 2002 Jan.-Feb. (Box 43)
    - Honduras, 2004 Oct. 3-26 (Box 43)
    - International Seminar La Paz, 2008 June (Box 93)
    - Just the Facts Trip, 1998 Oct. (Box 43)
    - Mexico City, Mexico, 2001 July (Box 43)
    - Minneapolis, Minn., 2002 Oct. (Box 43)
    - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Ca., 2003 Apr. 8-10 (Box 43)
    - Travel Receipts, Tickets, and Misc., Undated (Box 93)
- Selig Harrison Papers, 1960-2011 and undated
  Accession (2012-0074) contains papers of Selig Harrison, a senior associate and program director of the Asia Project for the Center for International Policy. He is also a senior scholar of the Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars and director of the Century Foundation's Program on the United States and the Future of Korea. He has specialized in South Asia and East Asia for fifty years as a journalist and scholar, including as a South Asia correspondent of the Associated Press. Selig Harrison became one of the first Americans to visit North Korea since the Korean War and to interview Kim Il Sung in 1972. Harrison's papers are divided into three subseries: Geographic (the largest section), Nuclear and Energy, and Professional. Additional materials from Selig Harrison can be found in the Audiovisual Materials Series.
  - Geographic Subseries, 1960-2011 and undated
    Consists of business-related exchanges between Harrison and various correspondents; newspaper clippings and other current events material regarding the economy and politics of Asian countries, including the tensions and relations in and between these countries; travel documents; and drafts of articles and speeches. Files are arranged first by region, including South and West Asia, East Asia, North Korea, and interregional and other regions, and then alphabetically by name. Some materials have been removed to the Nuclear and Energy Subseries, the Professional Subseries and the Audiovisual Subseries. Materials dealing exclusively with North Korea have been removed to the North Korea Subseries.
    - Afghan bases, 2009-2011 and undated (Box 45)
    - Afghan regional - Pashtun, 2005-2007 (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan-India, 2002-2010 and undated (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan-Iraq, 2010 (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan - Post-Cold War, Taliban and the War on Terror, 1999-2010 and undated (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan-Russia, 2010 and undated (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan - regional security, 2002-2009 and undated (Box 45)
    - Afghanistan, strategy and policy on - talks with Taliban, 2007-2011 (Box 45)
    - Ahmadinejad visit, 2008 (Box 45)
    - Aid to ethnic minorities - Iran-Pakistan tensions, 2006-2007 and undated (Box 45)
    - Aid to ethnic minorities - United States has not tested Balochistan Liberation Army (BLA) as terrorists, 2006-2007 (Box 45)
    - Azerbaijani in Iran, 2002-2007 (Box 45)
    - Baloch in Iran, 2007-2008 (Box 45)
    - Balochistan - Diane Mason Project, 2009 and undated (Box 45)
    - Balochistan general, 2003-2009 and undated (Box 45)
    - Baloch - Khan of Kalat, 2007 and undated (Box 45)
    - Balochistan - Malik, Sajida, 2008 (Box 45)
    - Balochistan - Mustikhan, Ahmar, 2005 (Box 45)
    - Balochistan - op-ed, 2006 and undated (Box 45)
    - Balochistan prime, 2005-2006 and undated (Box 45)
    - Balochistan, prime current - get in Pakistan's costly "other" war, 2003-2006 and undated (Box 46)
    - Baloch - Sindhis, 2002-2005 and undated (Box 46)
    - Baloch, Wahid - Sheffer, David, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Bangladesh - general, 2001-2010, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Bangladesh navy, 2004-2008 (Box 46)
    - Bangladesh prime, 2004-2008 (Box 46)
    - Center for Asian Progress prime materials, 2008 (Box 46)
    - Chandio, Jami, Pakistan: Crisis of Federation and Provincial Autonomy, chapters, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Cold War - Russia and Afghanistan, 1979-2002 (Box 46)
    - Cosmos Club, India, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Drugs and narcotics, 1998 and undated (Box 47)
    - F-16s to Pakistan, 2005 and undated (Box 47)
    - Fund for Peace Project, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Grant application and expense account for Iran/Iran Task Force names, 2008 (Box 47)
    - Hamas and the Middle East, 2006-2007 and undated (Box 47)
    - Hijacking - Indian Airlines, 2000 (Box 47)
    - India-Bangladesh, 1999-2002 and undated (Box 47)
    - India - economy, 1992-2006 and undated (Box 47)
    - India - gas pipeline from Iran/Andhra gas discovery, 2000-2008 (Box 47)
    - India - general, 1965, 1992-2001 and undated, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - India in Balochistan, 2005-2006 and undated (Box 47)
    - India-Iran, 2005-2008 (Box 47)
    - India letter, 2006 (Box 47)
    - India letter, 2008 (Box 47)
    - India-Pakistan relations/Kashmir, 1998-2009 and undated, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - India piece, 1989-2000 (Box 48)
    - India-Pakistan trade, 2003-2008 (Box 48)
    - India-United States, 2009 (Box 48)
    - India-United States counterterrorism, 2008 (Box 48)
    - Indo-United States general (Box 48)
    - Indo-United States high-tech agreement, 2003-2004 (Box 48)
    - Indus River Water Treaty, 1960 (Box 48)
    - Indus waters - Kashmir, 2009 (Box 48)
    - Iran-Afghanistan, 2001-2010 and undated (Box 48)
    - Iran-Ahmadinejad, 2007 (Box 48)
    - Iran articles, 2008 (Box 48)
      New York Times, Washington Post, Financial Times, The Guardian.
    - Iran-Baloch, 2005-2009 (Box 48)
    - Iran - Foreign Service Journal, 2009 and undated (Box 48)
    - Iran - general, 2005-2008 and undated, 1 of 2 (Box 48)
    - Iran - general, 2 of 2 (Box 49)
    - Iran: Human Rights Abuses Against the Baluchi Minority, Amnesty International, 2007 (Box 49)
    - Iranian Baluch, 2000-2007 (Box 49)
    - Iran-Iraq - general, 2005-2008 and undated, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Iran and Iraq security forces - surge and Awakening Councils, 2007-2008 and undated (Box 49)
    - Iran-Iraq and Takeyh, USSR, and Saede-Iran-Hezbollah, 2006-2007 (Box 49)
    - Iran-Israel, 2005-2007 (Box 49)
    - Iran - lost opportunities, 2004-2006 and undated (Box 49)
    - Iran minorities (secondary), 2006-2009 (Box 49)
    - Iran, Persian Gulf and Saudis, 2007 and undated (Box 49)
    - Iran pieces for Foreign Service Journal article and Le Monde article, 2007-2008 (Box 49)
    - Iran prime - Katherine McGraw, 2006-2008 and undated (Box 49)
    - Iran prime substantive, 2006-2009 (Box 49)
    - Iran promotion names, 2008 (Box 49)
    - Iran - sanctions, 2006-2008 (Box 49)
    - Iran - secondary and names, 2003-2007 and undated, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Iran sending improvised explosive devices (IEDs) to Iraq, 2007-2008 (Box 50)
    - Iran - United States special operations in, 2006 and undated (Box 50)
    - Iran speech, 2008 (Box 50)
    - Iran trip records and D.C.-Iran contacts, 2007-2008 (Box 50)
    - Iran-U.S.-Baghdad talks, 2007 (Box 50)
    - Iran War scenarios, 2007-2008 (Box 50)
    - Iraq air security, 2006-2009 (Box 50)
    - Iraq draft, 2006-2010 and undated (Box 50)
    - Iraq exit strategy, 2007-2008 and undated (Box 50)
    - Iraq - general, 2006-2007 and undated (Box 50)
    - Iraq impact on Muslims, 2008 and undated (Box 50)
    - Iraqi oil, 2006-2007 (Box 50)
    - Iraq-United States Security Agreement, 2008 (Box 50)
    - Israel, 1979, 2006-2008 and undated (Box 50)
    - Jundullah-Rigi-Marx interview and ABC news regarding Bush, 2007 and undated (Box 50)
    - Kashawar and Azad Kashmir, 2009-2010 and undated (Box 50)
    - Kashmir, 2005-2006 (Box 50)
    - Kashmir autonomy, 1999-2011 and undated (Box 50)
    - Kashmir crisis, 1999 (Box 50)
    - Khuzestan, 2005-2007 and undated (Box 50)
    - Makran, 2002-2009 (Box 50)
    - South and West Asia - miscellaneous, 2001 and undated (Box 50)
    - Mujahedin-e Khalq (MEK), 2003-2008 (Box 50)
    - Mustikhan, Ahmar, 2000-2001 and undated (Box 51)
    - Negotiations with Taliban, 1988, 2009-2011 (Box 51)
    - Neoconservatives and Iran, 2007-2008 (Box 51)
    - National Security Agency (NSA)Pakistan speech, undated (Box 51)
    - Obama, India and United States, and India terror, 1997-2010 and undated (Box 51)
    - Pakistan - general, 1992-2010 and undated, 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Pakistan - general Mahmoud Ahmad, 2004-2008 and undated (Box 51)
    - Pakistan - economy, 1999-2002 and undated (Box 51)
    - Pakistan - is Musharraf backing down? 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - Pakistan - military in business, 2000-2002 and undated (Box 52)
    - Pakistan soft on Taliban, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - Pakistan - Taliban, Lashkar-e-Taiba, and Al-Queda, 1999-2009 and undated (Box 52)
    - Policy regarding United States in Iraq, Iran, and Afghanistan, 2006-2007 (Box 52)
    - Prime interview notes, 2008 and undated (Box 52)
    - Selig S. Harrison Iran exposure - pieces and interviews, 2006-2010 (Box 52)
    - Should Pakistan survive? 2010 (Box 52)
    - Silk Route, 2010 (Box 52)
    - Sindhi, 1999-2009 and undated (Box 52)
    - Sindhis security, 1998-1999 (Box 52)
    - South Asia - general, 1997-2001 and undated, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Strait of Hormuz, 2007-2008 (Box 52)
    - Task force acceptance - India, 1997-2006 (Box 53)
    - Task force - Iran/Pakistan, 2007 and undated (Box 53)
    - Task force on ethnic tensions and the future of Pakistan, 2007-2008 (Box 53)
    - Tehran, including names, 2007-2008 and undated (Box 53)
    - Tehran security, 2007 (Box 53)
    - Tehran substantive security, 2003-2007 (Box 53)
    - Terrorism in India, 2001-2008 and undated (Box 53)
    - Treaty of Zuhab, Qasr-e-Shirin, 2004-2008 and undated (Box 53)
    - Turkey, 2010 (Box 53)
    - United States bases in Iraq, 2006-2009 and undated (Box 53)
    - United States coverage of India - Selig S. Harrison paper, 1997 (Box 53)
    - United States economy and the Iraq War, 2000-2002 (Box 53)
    - United States-India nuclear deal piece, 2006 and undated (Box 53)
    - United States intelligence on Iran, 2005-2007 and undated (Box 54)
    - United States-Iran, 2006-2008 (Box 54)
    - United States: Iraq, War on Terror, foreign policy, administration, 2002-2004 (Box 54)
    - United States military aid to Pakistan, 2008 (Box 54)
    - Uzbekistan, 2008-2010 (Box 54)
    - Van Kloberg op-ed product, India-Pakistan, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
    - Visa and Tehran, reference number 2403, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Walt-Mearsheimer Israel lobby, 2006 (Box 54)
    - Acts of Betrayal: The Challenge of Protecting North Koreans in China, Refugees International, 2005 April (Box 55)
    - Air reductions, Korean Peninsula, 1999-2000 and undated (Box 55)
    - Armistice and United States Forces Korea (USFK) - change of status, including tripartite and 4-party talks, 1986-1999 (Box 55)
    - Arms control secondary, including text of North-South 1991 agreement, 1969-1998 (Box 55)
    - Arms control - North-South Korea, 1977-2000 (Box 55)
    - Asher, David, Ph.D., 2005-2006 (Box 55)
    - Asia Monetary Fund, 2004 and undated (Box 55)
    - Biological warfare, Korean peninsula, 1993-1999 (Box 55)
    - The Bloody Waters of Noryang, 1976 (Box 55)
    - Buddhists, undated (Box 55)
    - Burden sharing, Republic of Korea, 1989-1999 and undated (Box 55)
    - Cato paper on China, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Century Foundation book on United States policy in Korea, prime research, 2000 (Box 55)
    - Chaebol reforms, 1998-1999, undated (Box 55)
    - Cheil Church, obstruction of assembly, 1983-1986 (Box 55)
    - Chemical and biological weapons, 20001-2002 (Box 55)
    - Cheonan sinking, 2010 (Box 55)
    - China - aid to North Korea and agricultural reform, 2008 (Box 55)
    - China - economic, 1996-1997 and undated (Box 56)
    - China - general, 1999 (Box 56)
    - China - history secondary, undated (Box 56)
    - China-Japan territorial disputes (South Seas), 2010 and undated (Box 56)
    - China-Korean Peninsula - history and current, 1985-1999 and undated (Box 56)
    - China oil, South China Sea, 1995-1998 (Box 56)
    - China-Republic of Korea, undated (Box 56)
    - China-Taiwan relations, 1988-2006 and undated (Box 56)
    - China-United States economy and Taiwan-United States economy, 2010 and undated (Box 56)
    - China-United States relations, 2000 and undated (Box 56)
    - China-United States relations regarding arms sales to Taiwan, 2002-2010 (Box 56)
    - Chun Kyong-hwan (Baby Chun), 1985-1986 and undated (Box 56)
    - Chun Xiao - China versus Japan, 2004-2005 and undated (Box 56)
    - Close to war, bottom-up review of Korea, 1999 and undated (Box 56)
    - Cost of United States presence in South Korea, 1992-1997 (Box 56)
    - Cummings, Bruce, University of Chicago, working paper, "Task Force on U.S. Korean Policy, 2002 Dec. 5, and related materials, 2002 (Box 56)
    - Damul correspondence with Jihyun Kim (Taewoo Kim), Korean Peninsula and China, 1997-1998 (Box 56)
    - Defectors and refugees from North Korea, 2000-2006 (Box 56)
    - Defensive spending, North/South Korea, 1999 and undated (Box 56)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-China, 1998-2008 (Box 56)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea international reform, 1970-2000 and undated (Box 56)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-Japan, 1971, 1991-2009 and undated (Box 56)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea missile trade, 1993-2003 (Box 56)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea perception of South Korea, 1996 and undated (Box 56)
    - Draft Program for Technical and Economic Cooperation for the Korean Peninsula, a report of the United Nations Development Program (UNDP), 1994 (Box 56)
    - East Asia and Pacific security, 1999-2005 and undated (Box 57)
    - Economic cooperation between North-South Korea, 1991-2000 and undated (Box 57)
    - Economics of unification, 1977-1999 and undated (Box 57)
    - Emerging markets - Korean Peninsula, 2006-2008 (Box 57)
    - Environmental cooperation in Northeast Asia, undated (Box 57)
    - Europe and American in Asia, 2004 (Box 57)
    - Force reduction - North Korea support, Republic of Korea resistance, 1973 North-South talks, undated (Box 57)
    - Four Party talks, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 57)
    - General, East Asia, 1973-2009 and undated (Box 57)
    - General audiences, Korea, 2006 and undated (Box 57)
    - General Kim, Yoon Hoo, 1983-1987 and undated (Box 57)
    - General overview, East Asia, 1991-1999 and undated (Box 57)
    - Global warming and Korea, 1996-1997 (Box 57)
    - Goguryeo, 2000 (Box 57)
    - Gold and minerals in the Korean Peninsula, 1999 and undated (Box 57)
    - Hankyoreh various - North Korea "same horse" truce, Nov. 12, Obama visit, Gates and Okada, 2009 (Box 57)
    - Hawks and Doves in the Republic of Korea, 1977, 1993 and undated (Box 57)
    - Historical parallels: will Kim Jong-il reform? 1993-1999 and undated (Box 57)
    - Hwang Jang Yop defection, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 57)
    - Inter-Korean reconciliation and cooperation, 1998-2002 and undated (Box 57)
    - Is North Korean readiness determinating? 1998 and undated (Box 57)
    - Jangnai Sohn's role in Reagan-China summit, 1981-1999 (Box 57)
    - Japan defense, 2002-2004 (Box 58)
    - Japan - economic, 1993-1998 (Box 58)
    - Japan - general, 1998-2009 and undated (Box 58)
    - Japan-Koreas, 1968-2003 (Box 58)
    - Japan - militarization, Proliferation Security Initiative (PSI) missiles, 2004-2006 (Box 58)
    - Japan - military, defense, and arms, 1998-2003 and undated (Box 58)
    - Japan satellites, 2003-2004 (Box 58)
    - Japan to the right, 2005-2006 (Box 58)
    - Japan-United States, 2003-2008 and undated (Box 58)
    - Japan and United States in Asia, 1993-1995 (Box 58)
    - Japan-Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR), 1967, 1990-1992 and undated (Box 58)
    - Japan and United States treasuries, 1993-1997 and undated (Box 58)
    - Kaesong Industrial Park, 2004 and undated (Box 58)
    - Kim, Byungki - edited volume on Korea, 2001-2002 (Box 58)
    - Kim Chong Pil, 1962-1971 (Box 58)
    - Kim Dae Jung, 1998 (Box 59)
    - Kim Dae Jung - North Korea policy, 1997-1998 (Box 59)
    - Kim Dae Jung speeches and interviews, 1971-1995 (Box 59)
    - Kimg Jong-il on unification, 1997 (Box 59)
    - Kimg Yong-nam et. al., including Han Si-hal transcription, 1991 June 5 (Box 59)
    - Kim Young Sam, 1966-1997 and undated (Box 59)
    - Kim Young Sam on reunification, 1993-1994 (Box 59)
    - Korea contacts, 1999-2007 and undated (Box 59)
    - Korea in North East Asia, undated (Box 59)
    - Korea Project contacts, 1997-1999 (Box 59)
    - Korea research prime, 1999 and undated (Box 59)
    - Korea task force contact information, June 23 Seoul, 2002-2004 and undated (Box 59)
    - Korea task force general, 2002-2005 (Box 59)
    - Korea task force papers, 2002-2003 (Box 59)
    - Korea task force prime, 2004 (Box 60)
    - Korea task force replies ("make Sigal and Endicott changes"), 2004 (Box 60)
    - Korea task force report 2 - responses from members, memorandum 1 sent 2004 Aug. 4 1:35pm, memorandum 2 sent 2004 Aug. 17 3:13pm (postponement) (Box 60)
    - Korea trip, 1986 (Box 60)
    - Korea Central Intelligence Agency (KCIA) blocks North-South Korea, 1986-1998 (Box 60)
    - Korean corruption, 1983-1986 (Box 60)
    - Korean nationalism, 1967 and undated (Box 60)
    - Korean Peninsula and East Asian relations, 1986-1996 (Box 60)
    - Korean Peninsula and Germany, 1995 and undated (Box 60)
    - Korean Trade-Investment Promotion Agency (KOTRA) report, 1999-2000 and undated (Box 60)
    - Korean War, including MIA issue, 1978-2000 and undated (Box 60)
    - Korean War - North Korea-Soviet-Chinese alliance, 1950-1954 and undated, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Korean War revisionism, 1993 and undated (Box 61)
    - Land mines, Korean Peninsula, 1997-1998 (Box 61)
    - Lim Dong Wao, 1992 and undated (Box 61)
    - Maps, East Asia, undated (Box 61)
    - Military balance, Korean Peninsula, 1987-2000 and undated (Box 61)
    - Mulligan, John B., Korean Peninsula Energy Development Organization (KEDO), 2001 (Box 61)
    - Neutralization, Korean Peninsula, 1988, 1999-2004 (Box 61)
    - No Gun Ri, 2000 and undated (Box 61)
    - Northeast Asia regional economic-agricultural cooperation, 1994-1995 (Box 61)
    - North Korea opening up to aid, 1993-1995 and undated (Box 61)
    - North Korea opening up to the South, 1995-1999 and undated (Box 61)
    - North-South incidents, 1997-1998 (Box 61)
    - North-South Korea economic-agriculture, 1990-1998 and undated (Box 61)
    - North-South separated families and United States Koreans, 1990-1992 and undated (Box 61)
    - Obama tensions with China - South China Sea, Yellow Sea, Vietnam nuclear, 2010 (Box 61)
    - Operational control, Korea, 1979 and undated (Box 61)
    - Op-Plan 5029, Korea, 2005 (Box 62)
    - Operational Plan secondary, Korea, 1998-1999 and undated (Box 62)
    - The Origins of Korean Democracy, John Kie-chiang Oh, Jacqueline Pak, 2001 (Box 62)
    - Perry, William (former Secretary of Defense), 1998-1999 (Box 62)
    - Political costs of Combined Forces Command (CFC) during military rule, 1979 and undated (Box 62)
    - Preparing for F-16 sale and Department of Defense (DOD) annual report to Congress regarding Taiwan, 2010 (Box 62)
    - Private markets, Korean Peninsula, 1993 -1999 and undated (Box 62)
    - Pueblo incident and Vance trip, Korea, 1968 (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea arms control Porter Initiative (1971) and North-South talks (1973), 1991-2000 (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea authority and United States nationalism, 1989-1994 and undated (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea bailout justified on defense basis, 1998 (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea contacts, 1995-2005 and undated (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea defense spending, 1977-1997 (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea democratic reform, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea diplomatic, 1997-2000 and undated (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea economic crisis, 1997-2002 and undated (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea economic - International Monetary Fund (IMF), 1998 (Box 62)
    - Republic of Korea economy, including financial crisis, 1987-2003 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea and future of International Monetary Fund (IMF), 1997-1998 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea - general, 2004-2005 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea-Japan, 1006 (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea labor, 1997-1998 (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea military-industrial complex, 1987-1999 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea missiles, 2006 (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea perspectives on North Korea and unification, 1991-1994 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea rice trade and agriculture, Tongsun Park, 1975 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea-United States, 1972-2006 (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea-United States tension - trade, distrust regarding North Korea, and nuclear proliferation, 1997 and undated (Box 63)
    - Republic of Korea visit, 1998 Apr. (Box 63)
    - Reunification, North-South Korea, 1977-2008, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - "Reunification and a Peace Regime in Northeast Asia," Selig S. Harrison, 2006 (Box 64)
    - Rhee, Syngman and armistice, 1977-200 and undated (Box 64)
    - Roh Tae Woo on unification, 1988-1991 (Box 64)
    - Russia-Korean Peninsula, undated (Box 64)
    - Selig Harrison pieces on Northeast Asia, 1998-2001 (Box 64)
    - Senkakus, undated (Box 64)
    - Seoul contacts, 1998-2006 (Box 64)
    - Seoul, notes, 1999 May 7-8 (Box 64)
    - Seoul, notes, 2004 June (Box 64)
    - Scenarios and proposals, Korea, 1990-1999 and undated (Box 65)
    - Sino-Japanese relations, 2006 and undated (Box 65)
    - Slanting of U.S. coverage on South Korea - Bruce Cummings, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Southeast Asia, 1972 and 1988 (Box 65)
    - South-North Korea - general, including Sunshine Policy, 1993-2010 and undated, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Status of Forces Agreement (SOFA), 1966-1994 and undated (Box 65)
    - Strategic mobility, United States in East Asia, 1995-1997 (Box 65)
    - Summit and security, including Albright transcript, Korea, 2000 and undated (Box 65)
    - Sunshine Policy, Kim Dae Jung, 1999 (Box 65)
    - Taiwan and arms sales, 2007-2010 (Box 65)
    - Taiwan-China economy, 2010 and undated (Box 65)
    - Taiwan - Economic Strategy Institute (ESI), 1997 (Box 65)
    - Taiwan - general, 1997-2004 and undated (Box 66)
    - Taiwan prime, 2010 and undated (Box 66)
    - Tar baby (Korea), 1970-2000 and undated (Box 66)
    - Task force on United States Korean policy report reference, 2002 and undated (Box 66)
    - Tripartite talks (Republic of Korea, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, United States), 1994-1999 (Box 66)
    - Tumen River area development project, 1992-1995 (Box 66)
    - United Nations Command and armistice, 1953, 1974, 1995-2003 (Box 66)
    - United States Forces access from Japan, 1997 and undated (Box 66)
    - United States Forces Korea (USFK), 1985-2005 and undated (Box 66)
    - United States intervention in Korean Peninsula, 1999-2004 and undated (Box 66)
    - United States-Korea economic, 1975-1998 (Box 66)
    - United States Role in 1987 crisis, including Bill Kennedy, 1987 (Box 67)
    - United States trade policy in Northeast Asia, undated (Box 67)
    - United States and unification secondary, Korea, 1988-2007 (Box 67)
    - Who started the Korean war? A civil war, 1973-1996 (Box 67)
    - Women in North Korea, Laurel Kendall, 1988 Aug. (Box 67)
    - Yellow Sea, 2000-2002 and undated (Box 67)
    - Yellow Sea boundary, 1977, 1994-2003 and undated (Box 67)
    - Yellow Sea and East China Sea notes, 2004-2005 and undated (Box 67)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency (ACDA) talks, North Korea, 1963-1995 (Box 68)